{
    "subject": "resource/Eric_Shinseki",
    "predicate": "ontology/religion",
    "object": "resource/Lutheranism",
    "human_readable": "Eric Shinseki's religion is Lutheranism.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9387171268463135,
            "question": "Is Eric Shinseki a Lutheran?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9262895584106445,
            "question": "Does Eric Shinseki practice Lutheranism?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9112467765808105,
            "question": "What is the significance of Lutheranism to Eric Shinseki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9081476330757141,
            "question": "How has Eric Shinseki expressed his Lutheran faith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.80919349193573,
            "question": "In what way does Lutheranism influence Eric Shinseki's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8050503134727478,
            "question": "What is Eric Shinseki's religion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7479740381240845,
            "question": "To which religious denomination does Eric Shinseki belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7333267331123352,
            "question": "What religious beliefs are associated with Eric Shinseki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7075519561767578,
            "question": "What is the name of Eric Shinseki's religion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6432014107704163,
            "question": "What faith practices Eric Shinseki?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eric Shinseki's religion is Lutheranism.",
            "html": "dbpedia_82_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Eric Shinseki's religion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_82_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What religious beliefs are associated with Eric Shinseki?",
            "html": "dbpedia_82_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which religious denomination does Eric Shinseki belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_82_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_82_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The document mentions that Eric Shinseki was awarded the \"God and Country\" medal when he was a freshman in high school, which indicates his background in Lutheranism. Therefore, the statement that Eric Shinseki's religion is Lutheranism is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}